export default {
  title: "German verbs (B1)",
  items: [
    {
      front: "arbeiten",
      back: "to work",
    },
    {
      front: "sprechen",
      back: "to speak",
    },
    {
      front: "gehen",
      back: "to go",
    },
    {
      front: "machen",
      back: "to do",
    },
    {
      front: "sehen",
      back: "to see",
    },
    {
      front: "kommen",
      back: "to come",
    },
    {
      front: "haben",
      back: "to have",
    },
    {
      front: "wissen",
      back: "to know (knowledge)",
    },
    {
      front: "mögen",
      back: "to like",
    },
    {
      front: "nehmen",
      back: "to take",
    },
    {
      front: "sagen",
      back: "to say",
    },
    {
      front: "glauben",
      back: "to believe",
    },
    {
      front: "fahren",
      back: "to drive",
    },
    {
      front: "sehen",
      back: "to see",
    },
    {
      front: "müssen",
      back: "to have to",
    },
    {
      front: "stellen",
      back: "to place",
    },
    {
      front: "warten",
      back: "to wait",
    },
    {
      front: "legen",
      back: "to lay",
    },
    {
      front: "spielen",
      back: "to play",
    },
    {
      front: "singen",
      back: "to sing",
    },
    {
      front: "bleiben",
      back: "to stay",
    },
    {
      front: "schreiben",
      back: "to write",
    },
    {
      front: "trinken",
      back: "to drink",
    },
    {
      front: "essen",
      back: "to eat",
    },
    {
      front: "lieben",
      back: "to love",
    },
    {
      front: "leben",
      back: "to live",
    },
    {
      front: "verstehen",
      back: "to understand",
    },
    {
      front: "helfen",
      back: "to help",
    },
    {
      front: "bringen",
      back: "to bring",
    },
    {
      front: "beginnen",
      back: "to begin",
    },
    {
      front: "suchen",
      back: "to search",
    },
    {
      front: "arbeiten",
      back: "to work",
    },
    {
      front: "finden",
      back: "to find",
    },
    {
      front: "lernen",
      back: "to learn",
    },
    {
      front: "sprechen",
      back: "to speak",
    },
    {
      front: "glauben",
      back: "to believe",
    },
    {
      front: "anfangen",
      back: "to start",
    },
    {
      front: "versuchen",
      back: "to try",
    },
    {
      front: "kennen",
      back: "to know (people)",
    },
    {
      front: "kaufen",
      back: "to buy",
    },
    {
      front: "verlassen",
      back: "to leave",
    },
    {
      front: "bezahlen",
      back: "to pay",
    },
    {
      front: "verlieren",
      back: "to lose",
    },
    {
      front: "vergessen",
      back: "to forget",
    },
    {
      front: "versprechen",
      back: "to promise",
    },
    {
      front: "gewinnen",
      back: "to win",
    },
    {
      front: "wechseln",
      back: "to change",
    },
    {
      front: "verkaufen",
      back: "to sell",
    },
    {
      front: "benutzen",
      back: "to use",
    },
    {
      front: "erzählen",
      back: "to tell",
    },
    {
      front: "verstehen",
      back: "to understand",
    },
    {
      front: "anrufen",
      back: "to call",
    },
    {
      front: "denken",
      back: "to think",
    },
    {
      front: "verbringen",
      back: "to spend (time)",
    },
    {
      front: "ziehen",
      back: "to pull",
    },
    {
      front: "möchten",
      back: "to want",
    },
    {
      front: "brauchen",
      back: "to need",
    },
    {
      front: "öffnen",
      back: "to open",
    },
    {
      front: "verletzen",
      back: "to hurt",
    },
    {
      front: "weinen",
      back: "to cry",
    },
    {
      front: "antworten",
      back: "to answer",
    },
    {
      front: "besuchen",
      back: "to visit",
    },
    {
      front: "wechseln",
      back: "to change",
    },
    {
      front: "reisen",
      back: "to travel",
    },
    {
      front: "erklären",
      back: "to explain",
    },
    {
      front: "begegnen",
      back: "to meet",
    },
    {
      front: "feiern",
      back: "to celebrate",
    },
    {
      front: "führen",
      back: "to lead",
    },
    {
      front: "bauen",
      back: "to build",
    },
    {
      front: "studieren",
      back: "to study",
    },
    {
      front: "bieten",
      back: "to offer",
    },
    {
      front: "lachen",
      back: "to laugh",
    },
    {
      front: "fahren",
      back: "to ride",
    },
    {
      front: "besitzen",
      back: "to own",
    },
    {
      front: "vermissen",
      back: "to miss",
    },
    {
      front: "erhalten",
      back: "to receive",
    },
    {
      front: "entdecken",
      back: "to discover",
    },
    {
      front: "wechseln",
      back: "to switch",
    },
    {
      front: "verhandeln",
      back: "to negotiate",
    },
    {
      front: "aussehen",
      back: "to look (appearance)",
    },
    {
      front: "beschreiben",
      back: "to describe",
    },
    {
      front: "verschieben",
      back: "to postpone",
    },
    {
      front: "untersuchen",
      back: "to investigate",
    },
    {
      front: "bewegen",
      back: "to move",
    },
    {
      front: "sammeln",
      back: "to collect",
    },
    {
      front: "sparen",
      back: "to save (money)",
    },
    {
      front: "klettern",
      back: "to climb",
    },
    {
      front: "vergleichen",
      back: "to compare",
    },
    {
      front: "wachsen",
      back: "to grow",
    },
  ],
};
